A useful tool within Word is
the find and replace tool.
This allows you to search through
a document for a specific word, and
then replace it with another word.
This could be very useful if you
have a large document and you need
to find instances of a word that
may appear a hundred, 200 times
and it needs to be changed quickly.
As an example, I have a letter on
the screen and I'm going to use
the find and replace tool to change
the word "data" to "information".
There are several instances
of the word "data".
And so I click on the
editing tool, select replace.
And the word I'm looking for
is "data" and I'm going to
replace that with "information".
There are three options here, so
you can replace, and that will
replace each instance one at a time.
So you can just confirm that this is
okay, or you can select replace all.
This will automatically search through the
whole document and replace every instance
of the word data with information.
It's good to be careful with
this because there may be certain
words are part of other words.
An example of this is
"night-time"/"nightmare".
So if you are looking to change the word
"night"into something else and those
words were present in that document,
it would automatically change the
first part of that word into whatever
you had decided to change it into.
So for this one here, I'm just going
to change data with information
and I'll go through one at a  time
so if I select replace, as you can
see, it's highlighted the word data.
So I click replace.
The second instance has appeared, click,
replace, and replace, and replace . Word
has now finished searching the document
and I can close that . And every
instance of the word "data" has been
replaced with the word "information".